in the notion AI is absolutely
incredible it can even write code and it
speaks English and sometimes on Google
as you know here are normal coaches we
are heavy users of notion they have been
a sponsor on this channel before on a
video where we build a web application
and we use notion as our backend and
database this video isn't sponsored by
notion but anyways I wanted to make it
because since our team was given access
to the Alpha version of notion AI our
minds have been constantly blown away so
let me show you some examples of what
this AI can do using the help me write
command we can ask the AI to write down
10 reasons why designers should learn to
code both in English and hangugo and see
what we get
[Music]
we can also use the brainstorm ideas
command to ask notion what should the
topic of my next video be so let's write
down video ideas for a programming
technology educational YouTube channel
and let's see what we get
[Music]
using the pros and cons list command we
can ask notion to tell us what are the
pros and the cons of learning to code by
yourself versus going to University
[Music]
let me know in the comments if you think
the AI makes good points or not notion
AI can also help you write a post for
your blog like for example why Ross is
better than C plus plus
another cool command among the many
commands available is the meeting agenda
command for example we can ask notion to
write down the agenda for a meeting
where we will be discussing if we should
move our offices to Thailand or Bali
wow sometimes I would like to write
poems to my favorite programming
languages but I never knew how to do it
thankfully there is a poem command for
that so let's ask a notion to write a
poem to the beauty of the rust
programming language
foreign
there are other commands that can create
social media post creative stories
essays job descriptions press releases
sales emails and more that work very
well but as a developer what interests
me the most is to see if this AI can
write code or not let's find out by
asking notion to help me write a python
code that sends a get request to The
Nomad coders website
foreign
[Music]
to write CSS code of a 200 pixel square
with a rounded corners and tomato
background color
or maybe using the go programming
language can notion write a function to
find an item inside of an array
as you can see this AI is incredible and
that's it for this video thank you for
watching if you like this content and
you would like to see more of it then
please consider giving me two clicks
like And subscribe that's all I need and
don't forget that if you want to learn
things like JavaScript python react
react native go dark flutter among many
others for absolutely free all you have
to do is click the link below to join
any of our many free courses that you
can take right now for absolutely free
with me click the link below and I will
see you there let me know in the
comments what was the command that blew
your mind the most mine is the pros and
the cons as well as the idea brainstorm